

# Ray Uhrig

# **Professional Summary**

Junior UX Designer with over twenty years of experience in the Education and Hospitality industries. Excellent reputation for resolving problems, improving customer satisfaction, and driving overall operational improvements. Well-versed in managing implementation and training while also handling all support functions for customers.

# Relevant Work History

## **Harmon Brothers Consulting - Vendor Relations**

Remote

04/2021-08/2020

- Interact with clients to determine 3PL needs
- Connect with a vet vendors for client needs
- Oversee referral commissions for HBC

### **Hive Digital Minds - Customer Success Manager**

Greenwood Village, Colorado

04/2017-08/2020

- Oversaw implementation, training, and support for SchoolBzz- a SaaS communication platform for schools
- Created training and support materials for SchoolBzz users
- Monitored metrics and developed actionable insights to improve efficiency and performance.

# SkyView Academy Charter School - Operations and Facility Manager

Highlands Ranch, Colorado

08/2010 - 06/2016

- Oversaw Facilities and Operations
- Oversaw all aspects of the Volunteer Program for all SVA families

# Realty Network Inc. - Real Estate Agent

Parker, Colorado

08/2005-08/2010

• Helped clients sell and find their dream homes

# Education

**Schiller International University;** Paris, France **MBA**: International Hospitality & Tourism 1993

**Schiller International University;** London, England **BBA**: Hospitality Management & Tourism 1990

**South Eugene High School;** Eugene, Oregon **High School Diploma** 1986

uhrig97@gmail.com (303) 472-9630 Centennial, CO 80121

### UI/UX

- User Research
- Information Architecture
- Wireframe & Prototype
- Usability Testing

# Soft Skills

- Customer Relations
- Hospitality
- Implementation Management
- Training and Development
- Data Analysis
- Online Support Services
- Problem Solving Abilities
- Marketing Development

#### Tools

- Sketch 3
- Marvel
- G Suite
- Trello
- Slack
- WordPress
- PC/Mac OS
- Replit
- Atom

# Licenses & Certificates

Jones College; Denver, Colorado Real Estate License 2005

**Careerfoundry**; Berlin, Germany **UX Design Program** 2021 **Front End Development** 2022